if you don't like trump, don't vote for he
if you hate the city, move out to the hills or to the field
if you wanna die, don't do that 
if you're allergic to the apples, eat a antihistamine before
if you hope that exist an operative sistem where you shuldn't pay for he, switch to linux 
if you are in a disagreement whit the chinease oprecion system, nerver go to china 
if you listen classic music in the car, you could develop deafness
if the cat pulls something valuable, acept the concecuences of have a cat in home
if you wolud mind have coronavirus, don't leave your home unless be necesary 
If you write a book, you must be aware of the errors that may comeif you start with linux, first you need to get used to using command consoleif you beginnig with linux, you first need get used the command console
if you read a book ensure of have a relaxed environment
if you check the price of the dolar in your country and you're in latin america, ensure of don't fall in depretion
if you knit a scarf for the cold times, use it after knit itif you argue with your love partner, relax and speak that calmly
if you have a toxic friend, leave their friendship for your mind health
if they do a machist act, hit him 
if you're a woman, you shall be feministif you believe in the christianity or some brahmanic belief, you need be aware for that don't be the ultimate belief and it's exactly equal than other beliefsif you belive in the christianism or someone brahamanic belief, you need be concient for that don't be the ultimate belief ad it's exactly equal that other beliefs
if you travel to the mountains, ensure that you have all that it's needed for thah
if you enterprise, it should a super important personal project
if you love someone, don't go fast, enjoy any moment and don't be toxic
if you have something important to do, ensure for do it the best that you can
